inboxviewergo.com 2014-01-21

# InboxViewer : Privacy Policy

Below you will find our privacy policy. If you have any questions, you may contact us here.

Your privacy is critically important to InboxViewer ("us", "we", "our", the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. Our Site contains links to other websites and products that are not operated by us. We use Neverblue Media in order to promote such websites or products. If you click on a third-party link or function, you may be directed to that third-party's website or prompted to install their product. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions, End User License Agreement or other policies of any website or product you encounter.

#### Information Collection And Use

While using our Site or contacting us for product support, we may ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information, which includes, but is not limited to: your email address, your first name, your last name and your phone number ("Personal Information").

#### Security and Privacy

Your privacy is critically important to us, but please remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

#### Log Data

Like many website operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

#### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

We use third-party analytics and advertising services for a variety of reasons, which includes: making our website more relevant and promoting our website to you through advertising. Our third-party vendors may use cookies in order to serve you ads on various websites across the Internet.

#### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in any email we send.

InboxViewer has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, terms or practices of any third-party websites, products or services.

#### Compliance With Laws

InboxViewer will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Site.

#### Business Transaction

If InboxViewer is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

#### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we discover that a Children under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us here.

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

InboxViewer may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.
